(Howard:)What happened to your thumb?
Yeah, I have ten fingers
and ten toes.
If I tell you a story about each of them,
we'll be here all day. Let's move on.
- What can I get you?
- Ah.
(Sheldon:)Seeing as I'm on vacation,
a piña colada seems appropriate.
(Sheldon:)Extra pineapple slices,
extra whipped cream...
(Sheldon:)...extra cherries, extra umbrellas,
and, uh, hold the rum.
Don't Iet me have too many of those.
(Penny:)Hey. What are you guys doing here?
(Howard:)We're grown men.
We drink at bars, heh.
(Penny:)No and no.
(Penny:)Everything okay
with you and Bernadette?
(Howard:)Oh, yeah, sure.
- You and Amy? Good?
- Oh, better than good.
(Penny:)Those girls text me every detail
of their lives as it happens.
(Howard:)I'm not signing a prenup.
All right, wolowitz, listen up. You
sign anything she puts in front of you.
(Penny:)You are the luckiest man alive.